[
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0e2f6233-0e58-47bb-9a74-572239f9b58a",
        "correctAnswer": "You need technology, you need the professions, but you also need something that speaks to the heart.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Technology decreases your ability to recognize beauty.",
            "The purpose of education is to build professional opportunities.",
            "Studying great art helps you see the interconnectedness of all areas of knowledge."
        ],
        "question": "President Gordon B. Hinckley said that a study of the humanities \u201cgives an aspect of living that is essential.\u201d He believed:",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "dbd772fa-e823-4cc6-9a42-74e4e9876720",
        "correctAnswer": "The aulos",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The trumpet",
            "The lyre",
            "The flute"
        ],
        "question": "What instrument did worshippers of Dionysus play?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "86080c77-032a-4296-83cd-e37bc5151961",
        "correctAnswer": "Romanesque",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Dionysian",
            "Maslow's hierarchy of needs",
            "Polyphony between form and function"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the style of the early Middle Ages that uses Roman arches, domes, and barrel vaults?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ff785de6-dc0e-42bb-bf0e-6d3628cfebdd",
        "correctAnswer": "Doric",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Corinthian",
            "Ionic",
            "What are the levels of a Gothic cathedral from bottom to top?"
        ],
        "question": "What is the name of the simplest and earliest of the Greek orders?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "46e4838b-62f5-4e8c-9cc4-461c8d22ee42",
        "correctAnswer": "ambulatory, triforium, clerestory",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "north aisle, south aisle, north transept, south transept",
            "nave, transept, aspe",
            "What do we call a vault created by a series of arches?"
        ],
        "question": "nave, crossing, choir",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "af072cd5-2ffb-41f6-8c73-297e11078548",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Oculus",
            "Keystone",
            "Triumphal arch",
            "Where was the altar placed in a Greek temple?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct!  A barrel vault",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "9db631ef-bc13-4171-aecb-c3a184365feb",
        "correctAnswer": "Outside, in front of the entrance.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Under an arch",
            "At the foot of the god or goddess statue.",
            "What is the name of the style of the early Middle Ages that uses Roman arches, domes, and barrel vaults?"
        ],
        "question": "Between columns and a concrete wall.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a041bd8e-b611-4f97-8448-6ef0231bc609",
        "correctAnswer": "Romanesque",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Maslow's hierarchy of needs",
            "Dionysian",
            "What is the name of the great domed church of Constantinople?"
        ],
        "question": "Polyphony between form and function",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a4637617-7a69-4f20-973b-b6fa718e1578",
        "correctAnswer": "Hagia Sophia",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Parthenon",
            "Colosseum",
            "What were the structures used to brace the outside of a Gothic cathedral called?"
        ],
        "question": "St. Sernin Basilica",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "6812b5d5-385a-486c-8385-fa6a9bee7468",
        "correctAnswer": "Flying buttresses",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Barrel vault",
            "Romanesque",
            "What do we call the philosophy that the world is rational and that we come to understand it through the Spirit?"
        ],
        "question": "Lintel and post",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "12a7d284-81c8-48bc-8aca-120503bdeb5c",
        "correctAnswer": " Scholasticism",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Life of the Mind",
            "Christianity",
            "What do we call the philosophy that the world is rational and that we come to understand it through the Spirit?"
        ],
        "question": "Pagan",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d4e49b05-ceea-4cbb-ba8c-ad660bfe2c17",
        "correctAnswer": "Scholasticism",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Life of the Mind",
            "Pagan",
            "What accounts for the differences between pagan and Christian architecture?"
        ],
        "question": "Christianity",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "36f7941c-5a84-4b99-92e2-91dd4eab3d84",
        "correctAnswer": "Christian services are meant to be indoors, to shelter them from the world whereas pagan architecture was open to both the sight of the gods they worshipped and the world.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Building materials",
            "Public life vs. family-oriented privacy",
            "Where was the altar placed in a Greek temple?"
        ],
        "question": "Aesthetic principles",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "40dd604a-0593-4a61-a653-620bb823c53d",
        "correctAnswer": "Outside, in front of the entrance.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "At the foot of the god or goddess statue.",
            "Between columns and a concrete wall.",
            "What is the name of the simplest and earliest of the Greek orders?"
        ],
        "question": "Under an arch",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "f5acba1c-dfab-4c32-b897-bc9f6037ce16",
        "correctAnswer": "Doric",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Ionic",
            "Romanesque",
            "What Greek order uses a scroll shaped capital?"
        ],
        "question": "Corinthian",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a9ae2a6c-6aba-4772-b39d-ce53aae9326c",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Corinthian",
            "Doric",
            "Romanesque",
            "Which brass instruments get their names because in ancient times they were made from a long, curled ram's horn?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Ionic",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "55b77918-dbf2-4fc3-b8c8-f721ea5bb322",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Trombone",
            "Trumpet",
            "Tuba",
            "Which brass instrument changes pitch by means of a slide?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Horns",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "70e00998-5c6e-403a-855b-7fffa880eada",
        "correctAnswer": "Trombone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Trumpet",
            "Tuba",
            "Indicate three percussion instruments:"
        ],
        "question": "Flugelhorn",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2e33d614-c8b9-4ea7-b749-b38dac2e16bb",
        "correctAnswer": "cymbals",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "recorder",
            "sitar",
            "bassoon"
        ],
        "question": "lute",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "10aebf59-2a76-461b-9cde-66e0d6e8d72b",
        "correctAnswer": "xylophone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "tuba",
            "french horn"
        ],
        "question": "piccolo",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "57d5a605-f1ef-4ef6-a77a-6e9cb6284a26",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "trombone",
            "Which statement is not true?",
            "The soprano is higher than the alto",
            "The tenor is usually a man"
        ],
        "question": "harp",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "9b7a294c-c99c-40b5-a926-b7900095228f",
        "correctAnswer": "Clarinet",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "What instrument did Benny Goodman play?",
            "Trumpet"
        ],
        "question": "The bass is lower than the tenor",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "08bfea00-73a8-4a7a-ae9f-7560acc0f321",
        "correctAnswer": "Brass instruments have reeds",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "String Bass",
            "Which statement is not true?",
            "The various string instruments relate to the ranges of the human voice"
        ],
        "question": "Drums",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "071fe7b0-8e56-4a1f-829b-72ae9f5bb870",
        "correctAnswer": "Trombone",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The harpsichord is a keyboard instrument",
            "Which brass instrument changes pitch by means of a slide?",
            "Tuba"
        ],
        "question": "Percussion instruments include the timpani and xylophone",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e27215a9-c641-483a-9d24-255fac2513d2",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Trumpet",
            "Which instrument plays the solo passages in Vivaldi's Four Seasons",
            "Cello",
            "Organ"
        ],
        "question": "Flugelhorn",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8929608a-9916-41d9-9825-41df7261e6f7",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Trumpet",
            "Which statement is not true?",
            "Many choirs include sopranos, altos, tenors, and basses",
            "A band is a group of instruments that does not include strings"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Violin",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3467463c-9191-48f8-9f29-255a9b2f91be",
        "correctAnswer": "Because they were originally made of wood.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Why do woodwinds have a softer, mellower sound than brass instruments?",
            "Because they must correspond to the ranges of the human voice."
        ],
        "question": "Strings are at the heart of an orchestra",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a96e36fa-546a-4e1b-a7fb-aa2b20d491d5",
        "correctAnswer": "The Paris Opera",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Because players hold them vertically.",
            "What is the setting for the Phantom of the Opera?",
            "The Rome Opera"
        ],
        "question": "Because they are plucked or bowed.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e9383b0a-0c64-42e4-8c68-beb0b6f0ae0f",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Metropolitan Opera",
            "Which statement is not true?",
            "The trombone is lower than the trumpet",
            "The clarinet is a woodwind instrument"
        ],
        "question": "The Venice Opera",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "423d4e4b-45ca-4e04-a426-1af0df9e7b89",
        "correctAnswer": "The trumpet is deeper than the horn",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "In mosaic, to make a picture an artist arranges pieces of",
            "Glass",
            "Tile"
        ],
        "question": "The trumpet is higher than the tuba",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "20cbd1b3-12f4-47ba-8794-37236f7cb815",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Stone",
            "When was oil-based painting pioneered?",
            "1600s",
            "1200s"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Any of these",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "800fdc6e-fbe9-4ed6-9abf-ab6b8ff98475",
        "correctAnswer": "copper",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "To make an engraving the artist takes a flat plate of soft metal and scratches the desired picture into the surface. Which soft metal is usually used:",
            "silver"
        ],
        "question": "1500s",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "61d253e2-0757-4937-90e8-ecb525e0eece",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "gold",
            "What is an artwork's medium?",
            "Where it's made.",
            "How it's made."
        ],
        "question": "lead",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "33a9f66b-fc1f-4852-a232-b2e3704f9152",
        "correctAnswer": "It lacks the fine precise detail of other forms.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "It's category or grouping.",
            "Identify a limitation of woodcut:",
            "The colored surface fades."
        ],
        "question": "Correct! What it's made of.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2d365b93-fb79-4eef-a09e-b74d976eb7a2",
        "correctAnswer": "days or even weeks",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The paint tends to flake off or become damaged.",
            "How long does it take oil based paint to dry?",
            "several months"
        ],
        "question": "The paint is immediately absorbed.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b943cd69-d2fd-43ef-846f-e6757ae7111f",
        "correctAnswer": "It lacks the fine precise detail of other forms.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "a few minutes",
            "Identify a limitation of woodcut:",
            "The paint tends to flake off or become damaged."
        ],
        "question": "a few hours",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "659e6252-b1e1-4493-a691-1c048381c190",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The paint is immediately absorbed.",
            "Which French monarch purchased the Mona Lisa?",
            "Louis-Philippe I",
            "Charles X"
        ],
        "question": "The colored surface fades.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e62e15ac-a2fc-44c3-97e6-470fe4364ec5",
        "correctAnswer": "The colors are fast and permanent",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Napoleon Bonaparte",
            "What is not true of a mural?",
            "The Last Supper is a mural"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! King Francis the First",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "cd7be4dc-cab0-4fb2-8067-37559ae160d4",
        "correctAnswer": "The palace of the French kings",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "It is painted on a wall",
            "What was the Louvre before it was a museum?",
            "An orphanage"
        ],
        "question": "All the statements are true",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0e1d129f-7f09-4ba6-8e45-a600a272c4dc",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A military barracks",
            "Bas in bas relief means",
            "Long",
            "Large"
        ],
        "question": "A hospital",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "353b7f9b-1a04-4315-bdbb-069907a1bdb8",
        "correctAnswer": " 1504",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Sharp",
            "What year did Leonardo begin the Mona Lisa?",
            "1520"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Low",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3a9afa59-c5c1-407c-b828-73ca36ef318e",
        "correctAnswer": "It allowed for ongoing revisions and blending of the colors.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "1400",
            "What did oil-based paint make possible in regards to the Mona Lisa?",
            "It allowed Leonardo to paint on a surface other than canvas."
        ],
        "question": "1516",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e797047b-f49c-41e0-aca2-92257cf38d36",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "It protected the pigment from water washes.",
            "What was the Louvre originally designed to be?",
            "A palace",
            "An art museum"
        ],
        "question": "It. provided a transparent background which reflected through the paint layers.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "015ce775-e9ef-435b-9ca6-eff12086ab23",
        "correctAnswer": "The Rule of Thirds",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Residence of the French Kings",
            "What is a simplified version of the Golden Section?",
            "The Allegory of the Cave"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! A fortress",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3015326d-add3-4bcd-931d-5259893851d1",
        "correctAnswer": "true",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Birth of the Blues",
            "Red and green are complimentary colors.",
            "False"
        ],
        "question": "The Pythagorean Theorem",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "bc32959f-a07f-49d6-8ec2-11face6261bb",
        "correctAnswer": "Texture",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Perspective",
            "Foreshortening",
            "Value"
        ],
        "question": "The 19th century artist Vincent Van Gogh is famous for his dramatic brushstrokes and thick globs of paint. Which artistic element is this?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "9d585777-c2b2-43f8-bd22-b8479cff1c15",
        "correctAnswer": "Green",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Red",
            "Blue",
            "Yellow"
        ],
        "question": "Which is not a primary color?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d6485327-18dc-46f5-8b7c-71c00490d278",
        "correctAnswer": "Repeating certain shapes, colors, etc.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Balance vertical patterns.",
            "Include lines running from left to right across the work.",
            "Include symmetrical and radial shapes."
        ],
        "question": "How do artists emphasize the emotional impact of a work?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ac2226dd-0f06-477a-9807-cc70da5ef3cb",
        "correctAnswer": "The contrast between light and darkness",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "False",
            "Chiaroscuro refers to________."
        ],
        "question": "Red and green are complimentary colors.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8ec9011d-d0ae-44f0-b704-2d993363ab4b",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "None of the above",
            "The Rule of Thirds",
            "What type of line is considered most pleasing to the eye?",
            "A slow curve"
        ],
        "question": "The formula for creating perspective",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "88507a44-bbfc-4c71-b420-8a83292a031e",
        "correctAnswer": "Texture",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A horizontal line",
            "The visual appearance of the surface of the canvas is called_______."
        ],
        "question": "A diagonal line",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0a34adf1-40ff-4605-aa3e-82080c2e801d",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Glaze",
            "Fresco",
            "How do artists emphasize the emotional impact of a work?",
            "Balance vertical patterns."
        ],
        "question": "None of the above",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a1b13b98-ae83-494c-9025-5d851cdb78c6",
        "correctAnswer": "Repeating certain shapes, colors, etc.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Include symmetrical and radial shapes.",
            "The 17th Century painter, Peter Paul Rubens, used a great deal of what color in \"The Stroke of the Lance\" to emphasize the violence of Christ's crucifixion?",
            "Black"
        ],
        "question": "Include lines running from left to right across the work.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0b391f15-a5b9-4223-9d37-44c0e0d1b5bc",
        "correctAnswer": "Red",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "White",
            "The 19th century artist Vincent Van Gogh is famous for his dramatic brushstrokes and thick globs of paint. Which artistic element is this?",
            "Foreshortening"
        ],
        "question": "Yellow",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "228b4296-dc5d-4063-b9c7-09e6234baf7b",
        "correctAnswer": "Texture",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Value",
            "Red and green are complimentary colors.",
            "False"
        ],
        "question": "Perspective",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "71bd729a-c4d1-4f0d-9a10-88bd4fc8f02a",
        "correctAnswer": "The Rule of Thirds",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "What is a simplified version of the Golden Section?",
            "The Birth of the Blues",
            "The Allegory of the Cave"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! True",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5a96e815-14d2-492a-abbe-fdfaad042727",
        "correctAnswer": "True",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A diagonal line indicates action.",
            "False",
            ""
        ],
        "question": "The Pythagorean Theorem",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "35c02e11-111b-4d70-b93e-8d15f00350ee",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Score for this attempt: 8 out of 10",
            "Submitted May 15 at 9:36am",
            "This attempt took 15 minutes.",
            "In the tragedy Oedipus Rex, Oedipus questions a blind man who refuses to tell him anything. Oedipus curses him for being so uncooperative; the blind man's reply is an example of what?"
        ],
        "question": "W04 Quiz: Theater and Cinema, Plot and Character Results for Doris Rush-Lopez",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ebf9c7f5-13b6-4830-a465-2289598d5692",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Complication",
            "Irony",
            "Peripety.",
            "Who wrote the play Oedipus Rex?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Foreshadowing.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b7753c2a-55a6-4781-b79b-926c5439e547",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Aristotle",
            "Arles",
            "Thebes",
            "What is the denouement?"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Sophocles",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "17a57a8e-1854-453c-ae29-172263064c00",
        "correctAnswer": "The part of the story from the change to the end of the story.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The resolution.",
            "The success of a story.",
            "What is the complication?"
        ],
        "question": "The part of the story from the beginning to the change in the principle character's fortunes.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b853888c-f326-4687-98b7-849b33aa455f",
        "correctAnswer": "The part of the story from the beginning to the change in the principle character's fortunes.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The success of a story.",
            "A condition aggravating an already existing one.",
            "According to Miracle Max, what is the greatest thing in the world?"
        ],
        "question": "The part of the story from the change to the end of the story.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "62b294b4-4a79-4c56-9158-bbc35e1f2d04",
        "correctAnswer": "A mutton, lettuce, and tomato sandwich.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "True love.",
            "A paper cut with lemon juice poured on it.",
            "What is high comedy?"
        ],
        "question": "Loose change in the pocket of a person who is all dead.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c315e846-e6c5-4ba8-b926-4aacfda2cd85",
        "correctAnswer": "Comedy of character.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A caricature.",
            "Physical comedy such as slapstick.",
            "According to Aristotle what is tragedy's proper pleasure?"
        ],
        "question": "Cartoons of political figures.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a127e779-e2b5-4adf-adad-29a80010b46a",
        "correctAnswer": "All of the above.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Cause us to pity the protagonist.",
            "To imitate action.",
            "To induce the emotions fear and pity."
        ],
        "question": "Make us afraid.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "57f247ea-592d-4648-9710-79bc680b5e4e",
        "correctAnswer": "Kills a man who demands that he get off the road.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Falls in love with a siren",
            "Rescues the city from a monster.",
            "Kills the king's assassin."
        ],
        "question": "What does Oedipus Rex do while traveling toward the city of Thebes?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "02882c94-ed30-4809-a00e-6f2824bc0b84",
        "correctAnswer": "The King and Queen of Corinth",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A Sphinx",
            "A shepherd",
            "The oracle or prophet of the god Apollo."
        ],
        "question": "Who raised Oedipus to be a young man?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7c8cffc1-b94c-44df-a9d0-dc5485e629ad",
        "correctAnswer": "The characters being presented with choices.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Flashback and reminiscences",
            "Episodic plots.",
            "Dramatic structure"
        ],
        "question": "What causes conflict in a story?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "14399c26-024e-4885-8f20-6deac8743fd5",
        "correctAnswer": "His real father",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "His brother",
            "The shepherd who saved him",
            "A sphinx."
        ],
        "question": "Who did Oedipus fight and kill on the road to Thebes?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ce3870df-ad73-401e-89db-fd4324601bee",
        "correctAnswer": "The events that led up to the beginning of the play.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A story without conflict.",
            "Events portrayed in the order in which they occur.",
            "A story told in a straightforward, linear fashion."
        ],
        "question": "What is backstory?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "345e675e-e4b7-44fe-a96c-f7ee000fa591",
        "correctAnswer": "The main character in a story.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The main character's opponent.",
            "An extraordinary character.",
            "A representative character."
        ],
        "question": "What is the protagonist?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "73f78d63-f1fb-43ad-a8a4-a0eb8bf06780",
        "correctAnswer": "King and Queen of Thebes",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "King and Queen of Corinth",
            "A sphinx",
            "The God Apollo"
        ],
        "question": "The tragic tale of Oedipus Rex begins when who received a prophecy?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "4c401726-1bea-4be1-8a2c-0f28bac57a60",
        "correctAnswer": "He rescued the city from a monster called the Sphinx.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "He exacts revenge on his mother.",
            "He fulfilled the prophecy.",
            "He killed the King's assassin."
        ],
        "question": "Why does the grateful city of Thebes offer the throne to Oedipus?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "28ceb143-efc1-4178-bcb7-8f1a65132efe",
        "correctAnswer": "Foreshadowing.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Complication",
            "Irony",
            "Peripety."
        ],
        "question": "In the tragedy Oedipus Rex, Oedipus questions a blind man who refuses to tell him anything. Oedipus curses him for being so uncooperative; the blind man's reply is an example of what?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "71b0c355-93bf-4b87-9305-9508cbee0d4f",
        "correctAnswer": "Sophocles",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Aristotle",
            "Arles",
            "Thebes"
        ],
        "question": "Who wrote the play Oedipus Rex?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "51950c90-4c87-4a80-a548-5e158edfea53",
        "correctAnswer": "The part of the story from the change to the end of the story.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The part of the story from the beginning to the change in the principle character's fortunes.",
            "The resolution.",
            "The success of a story."
        ],
        "question": "What is the denouement?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "9b2ec473-1485-4334-a220-1e83a02ddd89",
        "correctAnswer": "The part of the story from the beginning to the change in the principle character's fortunes.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The part of the story from the change to the end of the story.",
            "The success of a story.",
            "A condition aggravating an already existing one."
        ],
        "question": "What is the complication?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "95d5b48f-6d3e-4bdc-a580-6c081cf5874e",
        "correctAnswer": "A mutton, lettuce, and tomato sandwich.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Loose change in the pocket of a person who is all dead.",
            "True love.",
            "A paper cut with lemon juice poured on it."
        ],
        "question": "According to Miracle Max, what is the greatest thing in the world?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7f7d175b-f0e4-477c-a134-4129660995a6",
        "correctAnswer": "Repeating the same consonant sound at the beginning of several words.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The repetition of a vowel sound anywhere in the word.",
            "The repetition of a consonant sound anywhere in the word.",
            "Words that look like they should rhyme but don't (through, rough)."
        ],
        "question": "What is alliteration?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7d35c028-f22e-4501-9d0c-fdfa9cd03f05",
        "correctAnswer": "A short poem that represents the thoughts and feelings of a given author on some topic.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "A speech of a narrator or character from a drama.",
            "A story.",
            "A sweeping and long poem with a scope that is far broader than any other genre of poetry."
        ],
        "question": "What is a lyric poem?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "27e6054e-9471-4670-99a0-a1e628ab77bb",
        "correctAnswer": "A word's dictionary definition.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Connecting and comparing two things with a form of the verb \"to be.\"",
            "A word's implication and undertone.",
            "Language that goes beyond literal meaning and exploits its words' connotation."
        ],
        "question": "What is denotation?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ed7c7e8c-b207-4060-8fc2-d24276863e59",
        "correctAnswer": "14 lines of iambic pentameter.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Poetry that conforms to no restrictions.",
            "Perspective, all stories told from a point of view of some kind of narrator.",
            "Free verse without rhyme, rhythm and meter."
        ],
        "question": "What is the common form of all sonnets?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "041d34d0-ff7e-477b-a6b2-1dffdcec200a",
        "correctAnswer": "A foot",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Alliteration",
            "Assonance",
            "Consonance"
        ],
        "question": "What do you call one repetition of a metrical pattern?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3f408d5f-3100-420b-9cc4-7c09e4c57978",
        "correctAnswer": "A word's dictionary definition.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Language that goes beyond literal meaning and exploits its words' connotation.",
            "A word's implication and undertone.",
            "Connecting and comparing two things with a form of the verb \"to be.\""
        ],
        "question": "What is denotation?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a98fa6e0-4fd8-478a-9500-c0f64476415c",
        "correctAnswer": "Language that goes beyond literal meaning and exploits its words' connotation.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Connecting and comparing two things with a form of the verb \"to be.\"",
            "A word's implication and undertone",
            "A word's dictionary definition."
        ],
        "question": "What is figurative language?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "845197f7-5dd6-4809-94d8-61c20b9b1536",
        "correctAnswer": "A foot",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Alliteration",
            "Assonance",
            "Consonance"
        ],
        "question": "What do you call one repetition of a metrical pattern?",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c3d5b7f1-5203-41be-af54-3ddbefbb389f",
        "correctAnswer": "Foundations myths of a given society.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "True",
            "What are epic poems usually used for?"
        ],
        "question": "A dramatic poem is always an excerpt from a play.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "79cb8a8c-570c-41dd-8357-ff31bdd22ef8",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "To reveal the narrator's character.",
            "To quickly convey the author's thoughts and emotions.",
            "What is consonance?",
            "Words that look like they should rhyme but don't (through, rough)."
        ],
        "question": "To describe the effects of evil.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "dad7b44c-cfbd-49bb-b2d8-b91fbf872c9a",
        "correctAnswer": "The repetition of a consonant sound anywhere in the word.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The repetition of a vowel sound anywhere in the word.",
            "What is the thought of a play or film?",
            "Both the way the actors enunciate the text and the literary style of the text itself."
        ],
        "question": "Repeating the same consonant sound at the beginning of several words.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "f9b25d1a-7e37-470d-b2c7-05e2b4d53d59",
        "correctAnswer": "The themes, arguments, and overall meaning of the action.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The viewer's opinion about the play or film.",
            "What do we call it when words look like they should rhyme but don't (through, rough)?",
            "Slant rhyme"
        ],
        "question": "The rating.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "421fbed4-ff4a-481d-8bdb-d6e3f6e792d7",
        "correctAnswer": "Sight rhyme",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Near rhyme",
            "What do you call one repetition of a metrical pattern?",
            "Assonance"
        ],
        "question": "End rhyme",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "92e50b80-e403-47a1-b1c5-88796fa9ddbf",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Alliteration",
            "Consonance",
            "How many feet does iambic pentameter have?",
            "Four"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! A foot",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5e440756-75ba-4ccd-8ed9-8d52d6dfc149",
        "correctAnswer": "Five",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Eight",
            "What was not an important event of the Middle Ages?",
            "Building of monasteries"
        ],
        "question": "Six",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "f1490b78-f90d-42b7-be33-5b10847b05ce",
        "correctAnswer": "The Protestant Reformation",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The birth of modern nation states",
            "What brought back a modicum of prosperity and security in the second half of the Middle Ages?",
            "The conversion of the Vikings."
        ],
        "question": "The Crusades",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e7cecc06-11e2-49a1-a05e-43bf039656c7",
        "correctAnswer": "The idea is perfect and unchanging.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The invention of the printing press.",
            "Why did Plato consider the idea of a chair more important than an actual chair?"
        ],
        "question": "The philosophies of Aristotle.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e7762d10-88f7-4f77-b0c8-1e349f9a0c0e",
        "correctAnswer": "Reims Cathedral",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Ideas are free.",
            "Ideas are easier to create than actual objects.",
            "Where were the French Kings crowned?"
        ],
        "question": "The idea is unformed and therefore malleable.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "4aabc4fe-805f-4ddd-85bb-b19047c3a3f2",
        "correctAnswer": "Style",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Castillon",
            "Clovis",
            "What is the result of the many choices an artist makes regarding the medium, elements, and form of their art?"
        ],
        "question": "Paris",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c9a1d599-4162-4a80-b3c9-07a6482e7b8e",
        "correctAnswer": "Ascent of the soul into the intellectual world",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Tone",
            "Genre",
            "In the famous \"Allegory of the Cave,\" our text explains that leaving the cave or the upward journey represents:"
        ],
        "question": "Composition",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5e7dc17b-7e56-4d34-8ab6-c9586c61cb92",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Man's Search for Happiness",
            "Resurrection",
            "What was not an important event of the Middle Ages?",
            "Building of monasteries"
        ],
        "question": "Death",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5fd28e71-8f9c-487f-8c02-51a1a13f33ae",
        "correctAnswer": "The Protestant Reformation",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The birth of modern nation states",
            "What is not true about Plato?",
            "He favored censorship of music."
        ],
        "question": "The Crusades",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "cbc8a018-5c40-49dd-abe5-90852a5bc271",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "He believed young people should avoid slothful or lustful music.",
            "He believed the universe was created according to musical principles.",
            "In the famous \"Allegory of the Cave,\" what does the cave, or prison-house, represent?",
            "The birth of the world"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! He loved tragedy.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "fecf5872-8324-4f64-86b1-f500a9fbc08e",
        "correctAnswer": "Exemplary, of top quality, outstanding",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Agriculture past",
            "What does the word classic mean?"
        ],
        "question": "Industrial future",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "90a67aea-cc69-4cff-bcf8-92d7e2ea46a1",
        "correctAnswer": "Rebirth",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Revival",
            "Dionysian",
            "What does the name renaissance mean?"
        ],
        "question": "Out-dated or old",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d8365516-2696-4e4c-9e34-dc80f6b33166",
        "correctAnswer": "The idea is perfect and unchanging.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Human freedom",
            "Protestant Reformation",
            "Why did Plato consider the idea of a chair more important than an actual chair?"
        ],
        "question": "End of ancient times",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "05552a85-5bba-4164-b6f3-e93ab6adeff0",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Ideas are free.",
            "Ideas are easier to create than actual objects.",
            "What branch of philosophy deals with the question, \"What is real\"?",
            "Epicureanism"
        ],
        "question": "The idea is unformed and therefore malleable.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "71e68f32-c9d3-4c2a-9733-636e48980ec7",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Stoicism",
            "Cynicism",
            "The old saying \"Rome conquered Greece but Greece conquered Rome\" means:",
            "Greek soldiers used a trojan horse to sneak inside the gates of Rome."
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Metaphysics",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "1b928faf-652f-4b3e-bef8-a4aab57ebd6c",
        "correctAnswer": "Ancient, Middle Ages, Modern",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "German barbarians conquered the western half of the Roman empire in 500 A.D.",
            "Barbarian depredations, political disorder, and a drastic population decrease marked the beginning of the Dark Ages.",
            "In HUM 110, we will divide the history of the world into what three parts:"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Romans were so impressed with Greek culture that they made it their own and spread it throughout the world.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "fb50d1a5-f246-4e03-8704-db0db20219bd",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Mesopotamian history, Dark Ages, Modern history",
            "Age of Discovery, Renaissance, Protestant Reformation",
            "Which set of brothers were pioneers in the development of oil paint?",
            "Peter Brueghel The Elder and Peter Brueghel The Younger"
        ],
        "question": "Old Kingdom, Middle Kingdom, New Kingdom",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "66a892a5-cc8c-4a99-9eff-f2d231214127",
        "correctAnswer": "Hellenistic",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Petrus Christus",
            "What was the name of the Greek style as it spread throughout the Mediterranean world in the second and first centuries BCE?"
        ],
        "question": "Rembrandt",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "93ed29bf-01ec-478f-bccc-c9971c629605",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Byzantine",
            "Neolithic",
            "What was the technological advance of the Gothic style?",
            "The spinning wheel allowed for tapestries to be mass produced."
        ],
        "question": "Late Bronze Age",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2ce3b962-3278-49fd-980b-eac26ef06c92",
        "correctAnswer": "To influence the things of the natural world, to bring about a successful hunt.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Astronomical clocks.",
            "Why do we think the Lascaux cave painters created their art?"
        ],
        "question": "Evil spirits that might try to move into the cathedral were scared away.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3874436b-00dc-443e-97ca-459936f46795",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Because it's fun to make things.",
            "To give comfort to those who had died.",
            "Why do Egyptian paintings show some parts of the body straight on and some in profile?",
            "It was the best the primitive people could do."
        ],
        "question": "To express deep emotions without words.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b658b943-5bc8-481c-9e67-ae2e6ff7abca",
        "correctAnswer": "To show the objects from their best, most recognizable angle so that they have the most direct and powerful influence over the next life.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "To emphasize the importance of the physical body.",
            "What was the technological advance of the Gothic style?",
            "The spinning wheel allowed for tapestries to be mass produced."
        ],
        "question": "It's a joke, similar to a caricature.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "503c1b0f-2975-4e79-bad6-dcbfd67ca7d5",
        "correctAnswer": "Giotto",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Astronomical clocks.",
            "Which artist led the realistic revolution in painting in the 1300s?"
        ],
        "question": "Evil spirits that might try to move into the cathedral were scared away.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e8b93930-e5d4-431d-9296-9f9448262790",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Van Eyck",
            "Michelangelo",
            "What did the Byzantines seek to show rather than physical realism?",
            "An object's best, most recognizable angle"
        ],
        "question": "Rembrandt",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "b5947d9c-a4ab-4ecc-822f-304920ca7168",
        "correctAnswer": "Baby Jesus as a little man",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Natural settings",
            "\"Madonna and Child\" illustrates that Byzantine art is uninterested in a physical realism. This painting shows who with frontal views, stern expressions, and oversized eyes:"
        ],
        "question": "Political reality",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "bd668740-59e0-4ce8-af90-4e87223db062",
        "correctAnswer": "Roman arches",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "John the Baptist",
            "The Angel Gabriel",
            "What characterizes Romanesque architecture? (Select 4)"
        ],
        "question": "The Apostle Paul",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e6f58a69-d778-4314-b213-50fbcbc97f1d",
        "correctAnswer": "Stacked levels",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Intersecting arches",
            "High ceilings"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Barrel vaults",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "9dddeb36-cf4a-4ea4-ba3b-98121d423a6c",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Flying buttresses",
            "What did the Byzantines seek to show rather than physical realism?",
            "An object's best, most recognizable angle",
            "Political reality"
        ],
        "question": "Giant windows",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "500e1783-dd87-45ec-8109-48f774355fd2",
        "correctAnswer": "Build high walls with stained-glass windows",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "What did the technological advances of the Gothic style allow Gothic builders to do?",
            "Build concrete foundations"
        ],
        "question": "Natural settings",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7fe73f08-66d2-4f78-a495-593516785b0f",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Use steel rods to reinforce walls and ceilings",
            "What form of sculpture is uniquely Roman?",
            "Relief",
            "Monumental sculpture"
        ],
        "question": "Insulate walls, ceilings, and floors",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "a1d2db58-bffe-4908-8e36-4f15d77ac67c",
        "correctAnswer": "Expression",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Free-standing sculptures",
            "Does Hellenistic art favor form or expression?",
            "Form"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! The portrait bust",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7c69b4a9-bb37-4aa1-9f1b-925b06332c60",
        "correctAnswer": "Hellenistic",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Both",
            "What was the name of the Greek style as it spread throughout the Mediterranean world in the second and first centuries BCE?",
            "Late Bronze Age"
        ],
        "question": "Neither",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e066bfef-4258-40eb-8bbe-2d09d3e15168",
        "correctAnswer": "France and England",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Neolithic",
            "Who were the main combatants in the Hundred Years War?",
            "Scotland and Ireland"
        ],
        "question": "Byzantine",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "bde7ad98-95fe-4c2a-af30-ca3fb95a3d4d",
        "correctAnswer": "The Fall of Rome",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "England and Spain",
            "What event signaled the beginning of the Dark Ages?",
            "The 100 Years War"
        ],
        "question": "France and Scotland",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "85ca5533-2805-465e-9a2a-a1c75188e0ae",
        "correctAnswer": "Johannes Gutenberg",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Bubonic Plague",
            "Who brought moveable type to Europe?",
            "Christopher Columbus"
        ],
        "question": "The Fall of Greece",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "e74af992-86ba-4d9f-97d9-ef85df728a77",
        "correctAnswer": "Constantine",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "William Tyndale",
            "Which Roman emperor made Byzantium his capital?",
            "Augustus"
        ],
        "question": "John Wycliffe",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3ad144a4-53a1-445a-9cfa-f8e63ffe58bd",
        "correctAnswer": "The end of the Hundred Years War",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Maximinus",
            "What three events occurred in 1453, signaling the end of the Middle Ages?"
        ],
        "question": "Claudius",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "694006de-c511-4030-9b2e-b9b48e8583ed",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The understanding that the earth was round",
            "Where did most people live in 1453?",
            "Small towns",
            "Palaces"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! The invention of movable type",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "4b3127a6-890a-4d17-bb20-638c544febc9",
        "correctAnswer": "Farms",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Who were the main combatants in the Hundred Years War?",
            "England and Spain",
            "Scotland and Ireland"
        ],
        "question": "Cities",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "bb11ae80-de6a-492b-ada7-a6e0f1b7c27b",
        "correctAnswer": "France and England",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "What were the smallest living things anyone knew about in 1453? Select all that apply.",
            "Germs",
            "Gnats"
        ],
        "question": "France and Scotland",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "6f815f4c-8610-4fef-b8db-1c5218c54db3",
        "correctAnswer": "The Fall of Rome",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "What event signaled the beginning of the Dark Ages?",
            "The 100 Years War"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! Lice",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8427615b-f668-48b3-bfa4-0b076a3faae0",
        "correctAnswer": "Joan of Arc",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Fall of Greece",
            "Which leader inspired victory in the Hundred Year War?",
            "Saint Anthony"
        ],
        "question": "The Bubonic Plague",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c0c63a11-4293-4882-9802-79e4d578c92d",
        "correctAnswer": "Johannes Gutenberg",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "King Henry V",
            "Who brought moveable type to Europe?",
            "William Tyndale"
        ],
        "question": "King John II",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "3eaf98d3-d917-42e1-96bb-3429420c1b4f",
        "correctAnswer": "The Battle at Crecy",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "John Wycliffe",
            "What battle marked the end of medieval warfare?",
            "The Fall of Rome"
        ],
        "question": "Christopher Columbus",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "4fafa5cc-5c71-4421-a558-fe27c3954f97",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Battle of Calias",
            "Where did most people live in 1453?",
            "Small towns",
            "Cities"
        ],
        "question": "The Fall of Constantinople",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5777feb4-1dfc-41d2-8c47-d8d1d1c2a1c9",
        "correctAnswer": "Joan of Arc",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Which leader inspired victory in the Hundred Year War?",
            "King John II"
        ],
        "question": "Palaces",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2a42cf02-607a-435d-aa75-91dd688137be",
        "correctAnswer": "The Bubonic Plague, or the Black Death",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "King Henry V",
            "What catastrophe reduced the population of Europe in the 1300's and 1400's?",
            "The 100 Years War"
        ],
        "question": "Saint Anthony",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d6f732be-a166-41df-962c-da19954cd3cd",
        "correctAnswer": "Marco Polo",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Poor hygiene",
            "Who wrote a book about a Venetian party traveling to China?",
            "Plato"
        ],
        "question": "The Fall of Rome",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "33fdbc6b-02bb-443d-ba0e-8e3eefc40ee2",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Geoffrey Chaucer",
            "Which Protestant reformer insisted that churches be stripped of idolatrous images?",
            "Martin Luther",
            "Henry Vlll"
        ],
        "question": "Herman Melville",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "9d0cf17f-30b8-4ecf-8b91-cc75276032ad",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "John Wycliffe",
            "How did Plato's ideas affect the art of the Middle Ages?",
            "It made them more interested in natural phenomenon.",
            "It made them more interested in the human body."
        ],
        "question": "Correct! John Calvin",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "363eb54f-106b-4fac-ba2e-6795bcb8b7e5",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "It made them less interested in religion.",
            "Who proved the Copernican model of the solar system using a telescope?",
            "Roger Bacon",
            "Michelangelo"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! It made them less interested in the things of this world.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c4d62d95-a2a4-42c4-b519-ad790180add6",
        "correctAnswer": "Galileo",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "What was the key event of the Counter-Reformation?",
            "The creation of the Jesuits",
            "The Protestant Reformation"
        ],
        "question": "William of Ockham",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "94f554a4-9abc-4396-a008-d2cce34203f3",
        "correctAnswer": "The Council of Trent",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Which Protestant reformer insisted that churches be stripped of idolatrous images?",
            "John Wycliffe",
            "Henry Vlll"
        ],
        "question": "The 30 Years War",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7bf45421-777b-409d-b090-91b453f71e55",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Martin Luther",
            "What rich political leader was an important patron of the arts in Florence?",
            "Leonardo da Vinci",
            "Andrea del Verrocchio"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! John Calvin",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "d01f96b8-6b96-4d6c-b0f0-bb165f03ee35",
        "correctAnswer": "Lorenzo de Medici",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "What was the \"Middle Ages\" the middle of?",
            "The Greeks and the Renaissance",
            "The civilizations of the Greeks and Romans"
        ],
        "question": "Sandro Botticelli",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "61f2bfb7-6765-4ecb-8f10-bff9a66e33e4",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Babylonians and the Renaissance",
            "Who wrote a book about a Venetian party traveling to China?",
            "Plato",
            "Geoffrey Chaucer"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! The civilizations of the Greeks and Romans and the Renaissance",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "76ad1dbc-2bba-4846-b16d-b819ac03f207",
        "correctAnswer": "Marco Polo",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Who proved the Copernican model of the solar system using a telescope?",
            "Michelangelo",
            "William of Ockham"
        ],
        "question": "Herman Melville",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "338fd22e-9718-4f77-892f-a94bdf78f38d",
        "correctAnswer": "Galileo",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Who proved the Copernican model of the solar system using a telescope?",
            "Michelangelo",
            "Roger Bacon"
        ],
        "question": "Roger Bacon",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "6f97a798-c8c7-4078-9587-604fd847a03f",
        "correctAnswer": "So he could divorce his first wife.",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Why did Henry VIII lead England out of the Roman Catholic Church?",
            "So he could ignore the Pope."
        ],
        "question": "William of Ockham",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "6bf5f8a5-b58e-4285-a1d1-255124736234",
        "correctAnswer": "The burial place of Peter the Apostle",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "So he could be the Pope.",
            "St. Peter's Basilica was originally built over what place?",
            "The site of the Pentecost"
        ],
        "question": "So he could support John Calvin.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "43890420-b8af-4c2f-98f0-133674cae508",
        "correctAnswer": "Reconquista",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The hill where Peter preached to the Romans",
            "What did the Spanish call their war to take back Spain from the Muslims?",
            "La Resistencia"
        ],
        "question": "A battle ground won by the Warrior Pope, Julius the 2nd",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "c1f95070-a5d8-4ea0-9910-cadeda0eb7b7",
        "correctAnswer": "Empiricism",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Conquista",
            "What is the word for the belief that mankind's only access to truth is through the senses?",
            "historicism"
        ],
        "question": "Guerra de Libertad",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "1307c602-bb88-4385-affd-5bd1711bcd32",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "rationalism",
            "Before the murder, Macbeth sees a vision. What is it of?",
            "The King",
            "A sword"
        ],
        "question": "idealism",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "546a685a-dbe0-4bed-bcc2-da5d598b7dac",
        "correctAnswer": "Because his conscience will keep him from sleeping again",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Why does Macbeth say \"Macbeth does murder sleep\"?",
            "Because he is an insomniac"
        ],
        "question": "His wife",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "623f6184-bd0b-4db5-a7aa-be275dc64f80",
        "correctAnswer": "Their beards",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Because Macbeth will not sleep that night",
            "What makes Banquo doubt that the witches are women?",
            "Macbeth's doubt"
        ],
        "question": "Because Duncan is the King of Sleep",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "5da74adc-fb9c-4e21-ba93-330f6332cd0b",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Their hands",
            "What is blank verse?",
            "Rhymed iambic pentameter",
            "Unrhymed monometer"
        ],
        "question": "Their faces",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "04b48410-3758-4e31-b5b8-ccd1f2400d31",
        "correctAnswer": "Unrhymed iambic pentameter",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "How did Shakespeare adapt the story of Macbeth to suit the tastes of James I, King of England?",
            "He made Macbeth doubt.",
            "He made Malcom, James' ancestor, innocent of the murder."
        ],
        "question": "Rhymed monometer",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "521409e1-1505-4956-ac83-c4603c1ec2e3",
        "correctAnswer": "Their beards",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "He insulted Banquo by saying he is not a man.",
            "What makes Banquo doubt that the witches are women?",
            "Their faces"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! He made Banquo, James' ancestor, innocent of the murder.",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0efbc53e-cdd9-41e6-9cf5-3c6760138d24",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Macbeth's doubt",
            "What is a soliloquy?",
            "When the audience knows something the character does not",
            "When a character speaks their thoughts aloud to another character"
        ],
        "question": "Their hands",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "305d3fc2-a667-4223-9c15-c5b524a980dc",
        "correctAnswer": "When a single character speaks their thoughts aloud not intending other characters to hear",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "How did Macbeth get to be Thane of Cawdor?",
            "The original thane fled to England",
            "The original thane died in the war"
        ],
        "question": "When a character speaks directly to the audience",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0509a7ee-79a1-4c1c-a3b9-244c2996d50f",
        "correctAnswer": "The Thane of Cawdor",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The original thane was his father",
            "Of whom does Malcolm say, \"Nothing in his life Became him like the leaving it\"?",
            "The King of England"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! The original thane was executed for treason",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "1b993827-0299-42be-a7c8-98de021da2d1",
        "correctAnswer": "Duncan",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Thane of Glenco",
            "Who is the king of Scotland at the beginning of the play?",
            "Banquo"
        ],
        "question": "The King of Scotland",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0e284868-3efc-45ac-84b5-cf18d8798721",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Macbeth",
            "Who is the king of Scotland at the beginning of the play?",
            "Macbeth",
            "Banquo"
        ],
        "question": "Malcolm",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "bcd3c75b-d0ac-4b6a-be6e-f4d01b22fc37",
        "correctAnswer": "Duncan",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "When Macbeth hesitates, how does Lady Macbeth persuade him to go through with the awful deed?",
            "Calls him a coward and a drunk",
            "Insulting his manhood by saying he had no courage"
        ],
        "question": "Malcolm",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "fccc0bca-9c40-458d-a0c2-e804f4d0eebc",
        "correctAnswer": "Calling him a coward and not a man",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "What is a soliloquy?",
            "When a character speaks their thoughts aloud to another character",
            "When the audience knows something the character does not"
        ],
        "question": "Insulting him by saying he is not a man",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0ca47d8b-e71a-4ea6-a1b5-ee0f2d72472e",
        "correctAnswer": "The original thane was executed for treason",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "How did Macbeth get to be Thane of Cawdor?",
            "The original thane fled to England"
        ],
        "question": "When a character speaks directly to the audience",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "72628e54-e2b5-47c2-82f3-ed4faee0b19f",
        "correctAnswer": "The Thane of Cawdor",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The original thane was his father",
            "Of whom does Malcolm say, \"Nothing in his life Became him like the leaving it\"?",
            "The Thane of Glenco"
        ],
        "question": "The original thane died in the war",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "0d5e6bfd-e3ba-4259-97ef-dd5e6af5ab51",
        "correctAnswer": "She keeps trying to wash the blood off her hands",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The King of Scotland",
            "What is the nature of Lady Macbeth's madness?",
            "She has visions of blood on the ground"
        ],
        "question": "The King of England",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ce9856cd-96cb-4bc2-a7e9-98d71ed5c506",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "She has visions of the murdered king",
            "How did Birnam Wood come to Dunsinane?",
            "The invading soldiers brought battering rams made in Birnam Wood",
            "The invading soldiers lived in Birnam Wood"
        ],
        "question": "She keeps trying to wash a freckle off her hand",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "f0cc0a21-5820-4576-b1df-13d54a7c9a2e",
        "correctAnswer": "Scorpions",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The invading soldiers brought ladders made in Birnam Wood",
            "What does Macbeth say his mind is full of?",
            "Hornets"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! The invading soldiers camouflaged themselves with tree branches",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "7ee37025-0c44-4242-b15a-6543fd2adfc4",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Darkness",
            "What happens to Fleance?",
            "He is murdered",
            "He drowns"
        ],
        "question": "Witches' lies",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "2090af3e-516e-4cd1-984e-a737ad025315",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "He is put in prison",
            "Who says \"Double, Double, Toil and Trouble\"?",
            "Lady Macduff",
            "Lady Macbeth"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! He escapes",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "cdddc60c-1d79-48cb-a9e4-9d8fa4b33614",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Hectate",
            "What is the nature of Lady Macbeth's madness?",
            "She has visions of the murdered king",
            "She keeps trying to wash a freckle off her hand"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! The three witches",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "acb5cc10-e387-41cf-80e1-20e424f33820",
        "correctAnswer": "Malcolm",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "She has visions of blood on the ground",
            "Who is king at the end of the play?",
            "Fleance"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! She keeps trying to wash the blood off her hands",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "ce28ae06-0841-447c-87ef-a0e73430d353",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Banquo",
            "What happens to Fleance?",
            "He drowns",
            "He is murdered"
        ],
        "question": "Duncan",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "efa89856-85ab-40a0-a824-1ff2d7359a72",
        "correctAnswer": "He escapes",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "What three apparitions do the witches call up for Macbeth?",
            "An armed head, a royal child, and a tree branch",
            "A bloody child, a royal child, and wolf"
        ],
        "question": "He is put in prison",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "1e9c0437-4c56-4d28-bb66-510ff046f68a",
        "correctAnswer": " The invading soldiers camouflaged themselves with tree branches",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "An armed head, a bloody child and a dagger",
            "How did Birnam Wood come to Dunsinane?",
            "The invading soldiers brought ladders made in Birnam Wood"
        ],
        "question": "Correct! An armed head, a bloody child, and a royal child",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "f0e2d9c8-ba42-473d-a247-3d32499bcd3e",
        "correctAnswer": "To be born by Caesarian Section",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The invading soldiers lived in Birnam Wood",
            "How is it possible to not be \"of a woman born\"?",
            "To be born of Hectate, Mother of Magic"
        ],
        "question": "The invading soldiers brought battering rams made in Birnam Wood",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8ca26a92-52f7-45e4-8d13-2671dd4d6506",
        "correctAnswer": "",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "To be born of the earth as was Adam",
            "What does Macbeth say his mind is full of?",
            "Witches' lies",
            "Darkness"
        ],
        "question": "To be born of the Fae, Spirits of the land",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "8819532d-bea3-4c06-a359-f11f564d5466",
        "correctAnswer": "Scorpions",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "How did Birnam Wood come to Dunsinane?",
            "The invading soldiers brought ladders made in Birnam Wood",
            "The invading soldiers brought battering rams made in Birnam Wood"
        ],
        "question": "Hornets",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "971b5616-f2f6-44a2-90ba-e5ef65e4c0fd",
        "correctAnswer": "The witches say he would be the ancestor of kings",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Why does Macbeth fear Banquo?",
            "The witches say that he will kill Macbeth"
        ],
        "question": "The invading soldiers lived in Birnam Wood",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    },
    {
        "category": "Arts & Literature",
        "id": "6d9503c2-ad3a-40a4-b0b6-d4f2f4f800a0",
        "correctAnswer": "An armed head, a bloody child, and a royal child",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The witches say he would be king",
            "What three apparitions do the witches call up for Macbeth?",
            "An armed head, a bloody child and a dagger"
        ],
        "question": "The witches say he was greater than Macbeth",
        "tags": [
            "arts_and_literature"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "regions": [],
        "isNiche": false
    }
]